Rodrigo Nicolas Carreras

Software Developer at Comparaencasa.com

carrerasrodrigo@gmail.com

Summary

Hello I'm Rodrigo and I'm a software developer from Argentina. I have been working as a developer for more than 14 years, so I've had the opportunity to work with many technologies and specialize in the ones I like the most! My main skills are: Python, javascript, html5, css. I specialize in web development and I've worked with complex deployments on python and javascript using frameworks like Django, Angular.js and Bootstrap on cloud infrastructures like Amazon. I have experience working with different database engines like MySql Postgres, MS-SQL Server, Oracle and mongodb. I've also worked on mobile platforms, creating native applications for Android. When I started I used to work with languages like C, C#.NET, VB.NET, ASP.NET, PHP5, SQL Trans, VB 6. I'm not working with them right now but I sure know how to do it. I have experience working with desktop apps for different projects in areas like administration, field, etc. I know how to work with frameworks like QT and .NET. You can check my personal website and find more information about the projects I'm working on. Click here: http://carrerasrodrigo.com.ar/ Here there are some of the technologies I use on a daily basis: Python, Django, Pylons, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, less, Amazon clouds, Mysql, Sqlite, Postgres, mongo, SQL Server, Android, Angular.js, photoshop, nodejs, etc

Experience

Software Development at Comparaencasa.com

January 2011 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Python, Javascript, html5, AngularJS, React.js, django, php, amazon cloud, mysql, etc.

Software Development at The Kinetik

October 2010 - January 2011 (4 months)

I'm working with the following technologies: - Android - Python - MySql db - Web

Software Development at Mini App Stores

March 2010 - December 2010 (10 months)

Working on mobile applications for Iphone, Android and BlackBerry.

Participant in Startupbootcamp at Startupbootcamp

August 2010 - November 2010 (4 months)

I have been working on creating The Kinetik. ------ Startupbootcamp is a 3 month startup accelerator. We help you transform your startup idea by injecting cash, providing free incubator space and access to 50+ awesome mentors. By the end of the program you pitch at Investor Day. We are a northern European initiative affiliated with Techstars.

Software Development at CNA (Carnes naturales Argentinas)

June 2009 - May 2010 (1 year)

Working development software in * .NET plataform * MONO * MySQL database. * Django Framework

Software Development at Mobiliciouz

January 2009 - March 2010 (1 year 3 months)

Working on mobile applications for Iphone, Android and BlackBerry.

Software Development at Its Argentina

February 2007 - March 2009 (2 years 2 months)

I worked developing software in the .Net (2005) plataform, VB.NET, ASP.NET, using differents database like SQL SERVER 2000, MySQL and ORACLE 10.

Software Development at Global CEA (Consultores de empresas asociados)

April 2008 - February 2009 (11 months)

I worked developing software in the .Net (2005) plataform, VB.NET, ASP.NET, using differents database like SQL SERVER 2000, MySQL and ORACLE 10. I worked with Macromedia Flash and Macromedia fireworks too.

Customer service at Servicios Veterinarios NOA

2004 - 2006 (2 years)

- customer service - maintenance of medical records

Intern at GUMA SA

August 2004 - September 2004 (2 months)

- Intern in administrative area.

Languages

Español (Native or bilingual proficiency)

Ingles (Professional working proficiency)

Portugués (Professional working proficiency)

Skills & Expertise

Python

Django

JavaScript

AngularJS

React.js

Web Development

Ionic Framework

Android

MySQL

CSS

PHP

HTML5

AJAX

Mobile

Amazon clouds

Git

VB.NET

ASP.NET

iPhone development

Blackberry

HTML 5

Linux

Software Development

Mobile Applications

PostgreSQL

SQL

MongoDB

Education

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba

Computer Analyst, computer science, 2005 - 2009

Pio Leon

Busines administration, 1998 - 2004

Interests

software development, mobile development, dance tango, tango music

Rodrigo Nicolas Carreras

Software Developer at Comparaencasa.com

carrerasrodrigo@gmail.com



6 people have recommended Rodrigo Nicolas

"Rodrigo es un excelente profesional, responsable, dedicado, proactivo, inteligente, muy comprometido y con una gran capacidad de resolver proyectos difíciles en forma muy rápida. Es un referente en el desarrollo WEB, con conocimientos muy profundos en Python, PHP, MySQL, Linux. Siempre esta actualizado en las últimas tecnologías y siempre esta muy dispuesto a implementarlas en algún proyecto enriqueciendo de conocimientos a todo el equipo."

— **Sebastian Ferro**, managed Rodrigo Nicolas at Comparaencasa.com

"Rodrigo is a very intelligent person who has a very critical mind and a high level of motivation. He is a person who challenges the organizational or management paradigms in order to find new solutions or alternatives to complex problems. It is very exciting to work with people like Rodrigo, as his personality promotes a constant intellectual stimulation to the organization."

— Lucas Lezcano Velez, managed Rodrigo Nicolas at Comparaencasa.com

"Rodrigo Carreras ha sido el mejor compañero laboral que he tenido. Es destacable su habilidad programando para Android asi como tambien su capacidad de aportar buenas ideas."

— Paolo Rau, worked directly with Rodrigo Nicolas at Mini App Stores

"Rodrigo was a great boss, he gives me the right feedback everytime. Strong knowledge about the topic and an open-mind attitude!"

— Cesar Bernardini, reported to Rodrigo Nicolas at CNA (Carnes naturales Argentinas)

"Rodrigo demuestra buenos conocimientos y proactividad en diferentes circustancias y es un buen companero de equipo."

— Juan F. Moreno, worked directly with Rodrigo Nicolas at Mobiliciouz

"Rodrigo es inteligente, un excelente programador, y muy buena persona."

— **Raul Moreno**, was Rodrigo Nicolas's client

Contact Rodrigo Nicolas on LinkedIn